// const dayTenQuestions = [
//   {
//     question:
//       "The correct place to be wiped when wiping Khuf in ablution is to wipe …………",
//     options: [
//       "Over the Khuf",
//       "Under the Khuf",
//       "Back of the Khuf",
//       "Front of the Khuf",
//       "Inside of the Khuf",
//     ],
//     correctOption: 0,
//   },
//   {
//     question:
//       "Do we need to make another Tashahud after Sujud Sahwi (prostration of forgetfulness)?",
//     options: ["Yes", "No"],
//     correctOption: 1,
//   },
//   {
//     question:
//       "All are Sunanul fitra (the act that correspond to the nature of mankind) that we can get from authentic narration except ……….",
//     options: [
//       "Circumcision",
//       "Letting the beard grow",
//       "Tarawih in congregation",
//       "Cutting the nails",
//       "Shaving the pubes",
//     ],
//     correctOption: 2,
//   },
//   {
//     question: "Which deed is the dearest to Allah?",
//     options: [
//       "To offer the salats at their stated fixed times",
//       "To be good and dutiful to parents",
//       "To participate in Jihad (religious fighting) in Allah's cause",
//       "To give sadaqah",
//       "To help orphans",
//     ],
//     correctOption: 0,
//   },
//   {
//     question: "Which Salat is called Solatul wustoh (middle prayer)?",
//     options: [
//       "Salatul ‘Asr",
//       "Salatul Fajr",
//       "Salatul Magrib",
//       "Salatuz Zuhur",
//       "Salatul ‘Ishaa",
//     ],
//     correctOption: 0,
//   },
//   {
//     question:
//       "From authentic narration, in Islam, Aqeeqah (Naming…) comes up on the ……………………..day of birth.",
//     options: ["8th", "7th", "3rd", "10th", "9th"],
//     correctOption: 1,
//   },
//   {
//     question: "All are beneficiaries of Zakat except …..",
//     options: [
//       "Those employed to collect the funds",
//       "To free captives.",
//       "For those in debt",
//       "The wayfarer",
//       "The rich",
//     ],
//     correctOption: 4,
//   },
//   {
//     question:
//       "When performing Tayammam (sand ablution), how many times do we place our hands on the ground?",
//     options: [
//       "one time",
//       "two times",
//       "three times",
//       "four times",
//       "five times",
//     ],
//     correctOption: 0,
//   },
//   {
//     question: "Is dreaming after Istikharah a condition for its acceptance?",
//     options: ["Yes", "No"],
//     correctOption: 1,
//   },
//   {
//     question: "Is Zakat compulsory on a man that has less than 5 camels?",
//     options: ["Yes", "No"],
//     correctOption: 1,
//   },
//   {
//     question:
//       "In sharia, a traveler can wipe over his Khuf for three days while inhabitants can wipe over it for…………",
//     options: [
//       "one day and one night",
//       "two days",
//       "three days",
//       "four days",
//       "seven days",
//     ],
//     correctOption: 0,
//   },
//   {
//     question: "Prohibited times for voluntary Salat are …….",
//     options: ["seven", "six", "five", "four", "three"],
//     correctOption: 4,
//   },
//   {
//     question:
//       "Do we need to wash the corpse of a martyr that died during battle in the cause of Allah?",
//     options: ["Yes", "No"],
//     correctOption: 1,
//   },
//   {
//     question:
//       "Can we give out Zakat to our relatives, if they are among the beneficiaries of Zakat mentioned in the Quran?",
//     options: ["Yes", "No"],
//     correctOption: 0,
//   },
//   {
//     question:
//       "Qasr (Shortening of Solat) together with Jam’u (Combining of Solat) is allowed for ……………",
//     options: ["Sick person", "Debtors", "Traveler", "Prisoner", "Preacher"],
//     correctOption: 2,
//   },
// ];

// export default dayTenQuestions;

const dayTenQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Which tribe did the Prophet Muhammad (PBUH) belong to within the Quraish?",
    options: ["Banu Nadir", "Banu Quraiza", "Banu Umayya", "Banu Hashim"],
    correctOption: 3,
    justification: "The Prophet Muhammad (PBUH) belonged to the Banu Hashim clan of Quraish."
  },
  {
    question: "Which companion of the Prophet Muhammad (PBUH) was given the title 'As-Siddiq'?",
    options: ["Umar ibn Al-Khattab", "Uthman ibn Affan", "Ali ibn Abi Talib", "Abu Bakr"],
    correctOption: 3,
    justification: "Abu Bakr (RA) was given the title 'As-Siddiq' (The Truthful)."
  },
  {
    question: "Which year is known as the 'Year of Sorrow' in the life of the Prophet Muhammad (PBUH)?",
    options: ["610 CE", "620 CE", "630 CE", "619 CE"],
    correctOption: 3,
    justification: "619 CE is known as the 'Year of Sorrow' because the Prophet (PBUH) lost both Abu Talib and Khadijah (RA)."
  },
  {
    question: "What was the first mosque built by the Prophet Muhammad (PBUH)?",
    options: ["Masjid al-Haram", "Masjid al-Nabawi", "Masjid Quba", "Masjid al-Aqsa"],
    correctOption: 2,
    justification: "Masjid Quba was the first mosque built by the Prophet (PBUH) in Medina."
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the Prophet Muhammad's (PBUH) foster brother?",
    options: ["Zaid ibn Harithah", "Ali ibn Abi Talib", "Anas ibn Malik", "Abdullah ibn Abi Talib"],
    correctOption: 0,
    justification: "Zaid ibn Harithah was the foster son and freed slave of the Prophet (PBUH)."
  },
  {
    question: "Which Jewish tribe was expelled from Medina for breaking their treaty with the Muslims?",
    options: ["Banu Quraiza", "Banu Nadir", "Banu Umayya", "Banu Hashim"],
    correctOption: 1,
    justification: "Banu Nadir was expelled from Medina for breaching their treaty with the Muslims."
  },
  {
    question: "What was the name of the event where the Prophet Muhammad (PBUH) ascended to the heavens?",
    options: ["Laylat al-Qadr", "Laylat al-Isra wa Mi'raj", "Laylat al-Bara'at", "Laylat al-Quran"],
    correctOption: 1,
    justification: "Laylat al-Isra wa Mi'raj refers to the Night Journey and Ascension."
  },
  {
    question: "How many wives did the Prophet Muhammad (PBUH) have during his lifetime?",
    options: ["4", "9", "11", "13"],
    correctOption: 2,
    justification: "The Prophet (PBUH) had 11 wives during his lifetime."
  },
  {
    question: "What was the first surah revealed to the Prophet Muhammad (PBUH)?",
    options: ["Surah Al-Fatiha", "Surah Al-Baqarah", "Surah Al-Ikhlas", "Surah Al-Alaq"],
    correctOption: 3,
    justification: "The first surah revealed was Surah Al-Alaq (96:1-5)."
  },
  {
    question: "Which companion narrated the most Hadiths?",
    options: ["Abu Hurairah", "Abdullah ibn Umar", "Anas ibn Malik", "Aisha bint Abi Bakr"],
    correctOption: 0,
    justification: "Abu Hurairah (RA) narrated the most Hadiths, totaling over 5,000."
  }
];

export default dayTenQuestions;
